<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<document>
  <translation>
    <language_name_in_english>Russian</language_name_in_english>
    <language_name_local>Русский</language_name_local>
    <translator1_name>Yauheni Sobaleu</translator1_name>
    <translator1_email>sblfff@gmail.com</translator1_email>
    <translator1_date>2015-12-01</translator1_date>
  </translation>
  <page_title>
    <english>Introduction</english>
    <translated>???</translated>
  </page_title>
  <page_headline>
    <english>Introduction</english>
    <translated>Введение</translated>
  </page_headline>
  <audio>
    <text_intro_english>Download audio:</text_intro_english>
    <text_intro_translated>Загрузить аудио</text_intro_translated>
    <text_mp3_english>MP3</text_mp3_english>
    <text_mp3_translated>MP3</text_mp3_translated>
    <link_mp3>lang/en/fp/audio/mp3/00-Introduction.mp3</link_mp3>
    <text_m4a_english>M4A</text_m4a_english>
    <text_m4a_translated>M4A</text_m4a_translated>
    <link_m4a>lang/en/fp/audio/m4a/00-Introduction.m4a</link_m4a>
    <text_ogg_english>OGG</text_ogg_english>
    <text_ogg_translated>OGG</text_ogg_translated>
    <link_ogg>lang/en/fp/audio/ogg/00-Introduction.ogg</link_ogg>
  </audio>
  <phrase1>
    <english>"For when by reason of the time you ought to be teachers, you... need to have someone teach you the rudiments of the first principles of the oracles of God... Therefore leaving the doctrine of the first principles of Christ, let us press on to perfection — not laying again a foundation... of faith toward God, of the teaching of baptisms, of laying on of hands, of resurrection of the dead and of eternal judgment. This will we do!" —</english>
    <translated>«Судя по времени, вам следует уже быть учителями… вы сами нуждаетесь в учителях, которые бы учили вас основным истинам Божьего слова… поэтому давайте перейдем от основ учения о Христе к тому, что предназначено для зрелых. Мы не станем опять обосновывать… необходимость верить в Бога, учение о крещениях, о возложении рук, о воскресении мертвых и вечном суде. И мы сделаем это…»</translated>
  </phrase1>
  <phrase2>
    <english>Hebrews 5:12; 6:1-3</english>
    <translated>Евреям 5:12-6:3</translated>
  </phrase2>
  <phrase3>
    <english>(WEV)</english>
    <translated>(WEV)</translated>
  </phrase3>
  <phrase4>
    <english>Originally, the First Principle Studies were written in 1980, while I served the Lord during the formative early days of the Boston Church of Christ. They were revised in 2003 and 2006 to meet the needs and to confront the challenges of the Portland International Church of Christ. In Los Angeles in 2009 and 2012, I made a few more modifications. As of today, these same First Principles Studies are being taught to all the new disciples of the</english>
    <translated>Изначально серия уроков «Основы учения» (или «Основные истины») была написана в 1980 году, когда я служил Господу в ранние дни становления Бостонской Церкви Христа. Уроки были пересмотрены в 2003 и 2006 годах, чтобы удовлетворить возникшие нужды и ответить на вызовы, стоявшие перед Портлендской Международной Церковью Христа. Недавно, в 2009 году, после двух лет служения в Лос-Анжелесе я сделал еще несколько изменений. На сегодняшний день как раз этой серии уроков учат всех новых учеников в</translated>
  </phrase4>
  <phrase5>
    <english>City of Angels International Christian Church</english>
    <translated>Международной Христианской Церкви Города Ангелов.</translated>
    <link>???</link>
  </phrase5>
  <phrase6>
    <english>. God has greatly blessed these lessons as they have been translated into over 20 languages around the world. May the Lord continue to "solidify, unify and multiply" sold-out disciples everywhere for the evangelization of all the nations in this generation! And to God be the glory!</english>
    <translated>Бог очень благословил эти уроки, так как они были переведены более чем на 20 языков по всему миру. Пусть же Господь продолжает «утверждать, объединять и умножать» полностью преданных учеников повсюду для обращения всех народов в этом поколении! И пусть вся слава будет Богу!</translated>
  </phrase6>
  <phrase7>
    <english>Kip McKean</english>
    <translated>
      Кип Маккин
    </translated>
  </phrase7>
  <phrase8>
    <english>August 9, 2012</english>
    <translated>9 Августа 2012</translated>
  </phrase8>
  <phrase9>
    <english>Home</english>
    <translated>К содержанию</translated>
    <link>???</link>
  </phrase9>
  <phrase10>
    <english>Contact Us</english>
    <translated>Свяжитесь с нами</translated>
    <link>???</link>
  </phrase10>
  <phrase11>
    <english>© 2013 International Christian Churches (SoldOut Discipling Movement)</english>
    <translated>© 2015 Международные Христианские Церкви (Движение полностью преданных учеников)</translated>
  </phrase11>
</document>
