<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<document>
  <translation>
    <language_name_in_english>Russian</language_name_in_english>
    <language_name_local>Русский</language_name_local>
    <translator1_name>Yauheni Sobaleu</translator1_name>
    <translator1_email>sblfff@gmail.com</translator1_email>
    <translator1_date>2015-12-01</translator1_date>
  </translation>
  <page_title>
    <english>Persecution</english>
    <translated>ПРЕСЛЕДОВАНИЯ</translated>
  </page_title>
  <page_headline>
    <english>Persecution *</english>
    <translated>ПРЕСЛЕДОВАНИЯ</translated>
  </page_headline>
  <audio>
    <text_intro_english>Download audio:</text_intro_english>
    <text_intro_translated>Загрузить аудио</text_intro_translated>
    <text_mp3_english>MP3</text_mp3_english>
    <text_mp3_translated>MP3</text_mp3_translated>
    <link_mp3>lang/en/fp/audio/mp3/16-Persecution.mp3</link_mp3>
    <text_m4a_english>M4A</text_m4a_english>
    <text_m4a_translated>M4A</text_m4a_translated>
    <link_m4a>lang/en/fp/audio/m4a/16-Persecution.m4a</link_m4a>
    <text_ogg_english>OGG</text_ogg_english>
    <text_ogg_translated>OGG</text_ogg_translated>
    <link_ogg>lang/en/fp/audio/ogg/16-Persecution.ogg</link_ogg>
  </audio>
  <phrase1>
    <english>Introduction</english>
    <translated>Вступление</translated>
  </phrase1>
  <phrase2>
    <english>—</english>
    <translated>—</translated>
  </phrase2>
  <phrase3>
    <english>2 Timothy 3:12</english>
    <translated>2 Тимофею 3:12</translated>
    <link>???</link>
  </phrase3>
  <phrase4>
    <english>:  Everyone who wants to live as a disciple will be persecuted.</english>
    <translated>Каждый, кто хочет жить как ученик, будет преследуем.</translated>
  </phrase4>
  <phrase5>
    <english>Jesus was persecuted.</english>
    <translated>Иисуса преследовали.</translated>
  </phrase5>
  <phrase6>
    <english>Family</english>
    <translated>Семья.</translated>
  </phrase6>
  <phrase7>
    <english>Mark 3:20-21</english>
    <translated>Марка 3:20-21</translated>
    <link>???</link>
  </phrase7>
  <phrase8>
    <english>:  Jesus' family thought that he was out of His mind (brain washed; mind-control).</english>
    <translated>Родные Иисуса считали, что Он не в Своем уме («промывание мозгов», «управление сознанием»).</translated>
  </phrase8>
  <phrase9>
    <english>Mark 3:31-35</english>
    <translated>Марка 3:31-35</translated>
    <link>???</link>
  </phrase9>
  <phrase10>
    <english>:  Jesus prioritized His spiritual family above His physical family.</english>
    <translated>Иисус поставил Свою духовную семью выше, чем физическую.</translated>
  </phrase10>
  <phrase11>
    <english>Acts 1:12-14</english>
    <translated>Деяния 1:12-14</translated>
    <link>???</link>
  </phrase11>
  <phrase12>
    <english>:  This conviction produces conflict.  However, after His resurrection and ascension, His mother and brothers were disciples.</english>
    <translated>Такое убеждение приводит к конфликтам. Однако после Его воскресения и вознесения и мать, и братья Иисуса стали учениками.</translated>
  </phrase12>
  <phrase13>
    <english>Gossip and slander</english>
    <translated>Сплетни и клевета.</translated>
  </phrase13>
  <phrase14>
    <english>John 7:12-13</english>
    <translated>Иоанна 7:12-13</translated>
    <link>???</link>
  </phrase14>
  <phrase15>
    <english>:  Jesus was accused of deceiving people.</english>
    <translated>Об Иисусе сплетничали и обвиняли Его в обмане.</translated>
  </phrase15>
  <phrase16>
    <english>John 10:19-21</english>
    <translated>Иоанна 10:19-21</translated>
    <link>???</link>
  </phrase16>
  <phrase17>
    <english>:  The Jews — religious people — intensely persecuted Jesus through name-calling and character assassination.  Jesus' teaching always divided His listeners.</english>
    <translated>Иудеи – религиозные люди – неустанно преследовали Иисуса, приклеивая «ярлыки» и подрывая Его репутацию. Учение Иисуса всегда вносило разделение между Его слушателями.</translated>
  </phrase17>
  <phrase18>
    <english>Scope of persecution</english>
    <translated>Масштабы преследований.</translated>
  </phrase18>
  <phrase19>
    <english>Luke 23:1-3</english>
    <translated>Луки 23:1-5</translated>
    <link>???</link>
  </phrase19>
  <phrase20>
    <english>:  Jesus is condemned to a death by crucifixion through half-truths.</english>
    <translated>Иисуса приговорили к смерти через распятие, используя полуправду.</translated>
  </phrase20>
  <phrase21>
    <english>Jesus — who was perfect — was falsely accused and misunderstood by His family and killed by religious leaders.  What do you think will happen to you if you follow Jesus?</english>
    <translated>Иисус – не смотря на Свое совершенство – был ложно обвиняем, Его не понимали родные, а религиозные лидеры убили. Как ты думаешь, что с тобой случится, если ты будешь следовать за Иисусом?</translated>
  </phrase21>
  <phrase22>
    <english>The First Century Church was persecuted.</english>
    <translated>Церковь первого века преследовали</translated>
  </phrase22>
  <phrase23>
    <english>Acts 5:17-18, 38-42</english>
    <translated>Деяния 5:17-18, 38-42</translated>
    <link>???</link>
  </phrase23>
  <phrase24>
    <english>The Jewish leadership arrested the apostles for preaching the Word, because of jealousy.</english>
    <translated>Иудейское лидерство арестовало апостолов за проповедь Слова из-за зависти.</translated>
  </phrase24>
  <phrase25>
    <english>Those who persecuted the Christians thought that they were doing this for God, though in fact they were fighting against Him.</english>
    <translated>Преследователи христиан думали, что они делают это для Бога, хотя на самом деле они боролись против Бога.</translated>
  </phrase25>
  <phrase26>
    <english>The apostles suffered physical mistreatment.</english>
    <translated>Апостолам приходилось терпеть физические страдания.</translated>
  </phrase26>
  <phrase27>
    <english>Persecution did not stop the disciples from daily proclamation.</english>
    <translated>Преследования не остановили учеников, и они продолжили ежедневно возвещать Слово.</translated>
  </phrase27>
  <phrase28>
    <english>Acts 28:21-22</english>
    <translated>Деяния 28:21-22</translated>
    <link>???</link>
  </phrase28>
  <phrase29>
    <english>Everywhere, the church was highly controversial.</english>
    <translated>Церковь повсюду вызывала множество споров.</translated>
  </phrase29>
  <phrase30>
    <english>The church was called a "sect" (cult).</english>
    <translated>Церковь называли «сектой» (культом).</translated>
  </phrase30>
  <phrase31>
    <english>Since the International Christian Churches have the goal of imitating Jesus and the first century church, what will happen to us?  If a church is not being persecuted, what does that imply?</english>
    <translated>Что нас ожидает, если учесть цель Международных Христианских Церквей – подражать Иисусу и церкви первого века? Если церковь не сталкивается с преследованиями, что это значит?</translated>
  </phrase31>
  <phrase32>
    <english>Causes of persecution.</english>
    <translated>Причины преследований.</translated>
  </phrase32>
  <phrase33>
    <english>1 Timothy 4:16</english>
    <translated>1 Тимофею 4:16</translated>
    <link>???</link>
  </phrase33>
  <phrase34>
    <english>— Life and Doctrine</english>
    <translated>– жизнь и учение</translated>
  </phrase34>
  <phrase35>
    <english>Life</english>
    <translated>Жизнь.</translated>
  </phrase35>
  <phrase36>
    <english>1 Peter 4:3-4</english>
    <translated>1 Петра 4:3-4</translated>
    <link>???</link>
  </phrase36>
  <phrase37>
    <english>:  The world feels condemned by those who no longer participate in its sin.</english>
    <translated>Мир чувствует осуждение со стороны тех, кто больше не принимает участия в его грехах.</translated>
  </phrase37>
  <phrase38>
    <english>1 Peter 4:12-16</english>
    <translated>1 Петра 4:12-16</translated>
    <link>???</link>
  </phrase38>
  <phrase39>
    <english>:  Do not be surprised or ashamed by persecution, but be sure you are persecuted for righteousness' sake.</english>
    <translated>Не удивляйся преследованиям и не стыдись их. Будь уверен – ты страдаешь за правду.</translated>
  </phrase39>
  <phrase40>
    <english>Doctrine</english>
    <translated>Учение.</translated>
  </phrase40>
  <phrase41>
    <english>Preaching the Word —</english>
    <translated>Проповедь Слова –</translated>
  </phrase41>
  <phrase42>
    <english>John 15:18-20, 16:1-4</english>
    <translated>Иоанна 15:18-20; 16:1-4</translated>
    <link>???</link>
  </phrase42>
  <phrase43>
    <english>Jesus warns that persecution comes to those who preach the same message as Him.</english>
    <translated>Иисус предупреждал, что тех, кто проповедует то же, что и Он, будут преследовать.</translated>
  </phrase43>
  <phrase44>
    <english>Jesus warns that the price of hatred is certain, and perhaps even death.</english>
    <translated>Иисус предупреждал, что ненависть людей не обойдется нам бесплатно, возможно даже, что это будет стоить нам жизни.</translated>
  </phrase44>
  <phrase45>
    <english>Narrow Road of Salvation —</english>
    <translated>Узкий путь спасения – </translated>
  </phrase45>
  <phrase46>
    <english>Matthew 7:13-14</english>
    <translated>Матфея 7:13-14</translated>
    <link>???</link>
  </phrase46>
  <phrase47>
    <english>Acts 4:12</english>
    <translated>Деяния 4:12</translated>
    <link>???</link>
  </phrase47>
  <phrase48>
    <english>:  Only an individual who believes in Jesus is saved.  (This truth condemns atheists, polytheists, Jews, Muslims, Hindus, Buddhists, etc...)</english>
    <translated>Только тот, кто верит в Иисуса, спасен. (Эта истина осуждает атеистов, политеистов, иудеев, мусульман, индуистов, буддистов и т. д.).</translated>
  </phrase48>
  <phrase49>
    <english>Acts 2:36-38</english>
    <translated>Деяния 2:36-38</translated>
    <link>???</link>
  </phrase49>
  <phrase50>
    <english>:  Only an adult who is water baptized for the forgiveness of sins is saved.  (This truth condemns those who practice infant baptism and "praying Jesus into your heart" as doctrines of salvation.)</english>
    <translated>олько взрослый человек, принявший водное крещение для прощения грехов, спасен. (Эта истина осуждает тех, кто практикует крещение младенцев и «молитву Иисусу в своем сердце» как доктрины спасения).</translated>
  </phrase50>
  <phrase51>
    <english>Matthew 28:19-20</english>
    <translated>Матфея 28:19-20</translated>
    <link>???</link>
  </phrase51>
  <phrase52>
    <english>:  Only the person who makes the decision to be baptized as a disciple is saved.  (This truth condemns those who may baptize for remission of sins, but are not made into disciples before and after baptism.)</english>
    <translated>Только человек, принявший решение креститься как ученик, спасен. (Эта истина осуждает тех, кто крестятся для прощения грехов, но не становятся учениками до и после крещения).</translated>
  </phrase52>
  <phrase53>
    <english>We do not condemn the lost; they are condemned already.  However, when the lost are confronted doctrinally about their condition before God, they will repent, run or persecute.</english>
    <translated>Мы не осуждаем потерянных, они уже и так осуждены. Однако когда потерянным прямо говорят о ситуации, в которой они находятся перед Богом, они делают одно из трех: каются, убегают или начинают преследования.</translated>
  </phrase53>
  <phrase54>
    <english>Doctrine of discipling</english>
    <translated>Доктрина о наставничестве в</translated>
  </phrase54>
  <phrase55>
    <english>Matthew 28:19-20</english>
    <translated>Матфея 28:19-20</translated>
    <link>???</link>
  </phrase55>
  <phrase56>
    <english>:  Discipling, calling people to obey the Word of God, is often viewed by the world as controlling.</english>
    <translated>Наставничество – призыв подчиняться Слову Бога – часто рассматривается миром как контроль.</translated>
  </phrase56>
  <phrase57>
    <english>Our attitude about persecution</english>
    <translated>Наше отношение к преследованиям.</translated>
  </phrase57>
  <phrase58>
    <english>Matthew 5:10-12</english>
    <translated>Матфея 5:10-12</translated>
    <link>???</link>
  </phrase58>
  <phrase59>
    <english>Do not fear persecution.  Do not care what men think about you, only God.</english>
    <translated>Не бойся преследований. Не имеет значения, что о тебе думают люди, а только то, что о тебе думает Бог.</translated>
  </phrase59>
  <phrase60>
    <english>Rejoice!  You are not alone, since they persecuted both Jesus and the prophets.</english>
    <translated>Радуйся! Ты не один – преследовали и Иисуса, и пророков.</translated>
  </phrase60>
  <phrase61>
    <english>Ephesians 6:10-18</english>
    <translated>Ефесянам 6:10-18</translated>
    <link>???</link>
  </phrase61>
  <phrase62>
    <english>Satan is behind all persecution.  Only God and His spiritual armor will give you the victory over the world.</english>
    <translated>За всеми преследованиями стоит сатана. Только Бог и Его духовные доспехи обеспечат тебе победу над миром.</translated>
  </phrase62>
  <phrase63>
    <english>Conclusion</english>
    <translated>Заключение.</translated>
  </phrase63>
  <phrase64>
    <english>— The International Christian Churches are a controversial Christian movement.  Some call us a cult and accuse us of both brain-washing and mind-control.  Many false rumors and half-truths have been spread.  Newspaper articles, television shows and especially the internet have slandered the ICC, and yet, the facts are that lives have been radically changed, marriages have been healed, drug addicts have been freed, the poor have been fed and cared for, and this rapidly growing movement — The SoldOut Movement — is spreading around the world in this generation!  Just like the first century!</english>
    <translated>Международные Христианские Церкви являются движением, вызывающим много споров и критики. Некоторые называют нас культом и обвиняют в «промывании мозгов» и управлении сознанием. Распространялось множество лживых и полуправдивых слухов. Клевета звучала в газетных статьях, телевизионных шоу и особенно в интернете. Однако факт остается фактом: жизни радикально меняются, браки исцеляются, наркоманы избавляются от своей зависимости, бедные получают еду и заботу, и быстрорастущее Движение полностью преданных учеников распространяется по всему миру в этом поколении! Прямо как в первом веке!</translated>
  </phrase64>
  <phrase65>
    <english>* The Persecution study has been proven to be most helpful after the</english>
    <translated>Урок «Преследования» очень полезно после урока</translated>
  </phrase65>
  <phrase66>
    <english>Discipleship</english>
    <translated>«Ученичество</translated>
    <link>???</link>
  </phrase66>
  <phrase67>
    <english>study.</english>
    <translated>".</translated>
  </phrase67>
  <phrase68>
    <english>(See</english>
    <translated>Ссылки:</translated>
  </phrase68>
  <phrase69>
    <english>caicc.net</english>
    <translated>caicc.net</translated>
    <link>???</link>
  </phrase69>
  <phrase70>
    <english>,</english>
    <translated>,</translated>
  </phrase70>
  <phrase71>
    <english>usd21.org</english>
    <translated>usd21.org</translated>
    <link>???</link>
  </phrase71>
  <phrase72>
    <english>and</english>
    <translated>и</translated>
  </phrase72>
  <phrase73>
    <english>KipMcKean.org</english>
    <translated>KipMcKean.org</translated>
    <link>???</link>
  </phrase73>
  <phrase74>
    <english>)</english>
    <translated>)</translated>
  </phrase74>
  <phrase75>
    <english>Home</english>
    <translated>К содержанию</translated>
    <link>???</link>
  </phrase75>
  <phrase76>
    <english>Contact Us</english>
    <translated>Свяжитесь с нами</translated>
    <link>???</link>
  </phrase76>
  <phrase77>
    <english>© 2013 International Christian Churches (SoldOut Discipling Movement)</english>
    <translated>© 2015 Международные Христианские Церкви (Движение полностью преданных учеников)</translated>
  </phrase77>
</document>
